{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"260/20",
			"answer":"260/20",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"100/50",
			"answer":"100/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"684/57",
			"answer":"684/57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"156/78",
			"answer":"156/78",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"186/93",
			"answer":"186/93",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"310/31",
			"answer":"310/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"260/20",
			"answer":"260/20",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"100/50",
			"answer":"100/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"684/57",
			"answer":"684/57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"156/78",
			"answer":"156/78",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"35.04/0.003",
			"answer":"35.04/0.003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"645.5/5",
			"answer":"645.5/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.049/0.09",
			"answer":"5.049/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.0904/0.08",
			"answer":"0.0904/0.08",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.0024/8",
			"answer":"0.0024/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"99.84/0.04",
			"answer":"99.84/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"208.8/0.08",
			"answer":"208.8/0.08",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.974/0.2",
			"answer":"2.974/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"16.52/0.7",
			"answer":"16.52/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.9126/0.3",
			"answer":"0.9126/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}